

Sebastiaan Hoejenbos

CREATIVE ENGINEER

Strong focus on modern web and mobile applications.

I've been working with the web for more than 10 years. What inspires me is how the web changes our everyday lives.

The future is about context. I hope to design, build and think about these concepts so they don't dictate but enrich our everyday lives.



Profile

Schipluidenlaan 127
5035KE Tilburg
Netherlands

Please ask me, would love to talk!

in linkedin.com/sebastiaanhoejenbos

@windandforest



Experience

Hinttech Creative

CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIST

Mar 2013 - Present

As a creative engineer / technologist at Hinttech I'm involved in projects at different stages. From branstorming, concepting to providing an accurate estimate of the requested functionality.

As a member of the projectteam I will try to inspire my colleagues by providing them with new concepts and fresh insights.

Basisschool Klinkers

ADVISOR Feb 2014 – Present

As an advisor I work with the team at bs. Klinkers on building a web based platform for teachers to track the progress of students.

Tripitch Mediacreatives

SENIOR ENGINEER

Jan 2012 - Feb 2013

Functional Design, Prototyping, Front and Backend Webdevelopment, Database- and API Architecture.

Bluebased

CONSULTANT

Sep 2000 - Dec 2011



Concepting

Solution Architect

Web Development

Mobile Development

•••••

•••••

•••••

Interests

Concepting New technologies Web Development Realtime Web Mobile Development

Psychology

I spend way to little time playing Golf, Mountainbiking and Kitesurfing.□

Education

Hogeschool 's Hertogenbosch

INFORMATICA 1998 – 2000